The next part,
I'll just read it to you.
He talks
about these beings, these very powerful
beings. They were very kind
in their last life, very generous.
They didn't study back then, and they did
n't understand most things. But
because they were so generous,
they were reborn as very powerful and rich
beings.
And
then he talks about how if they
came from their own past,
they couldn't change. And that
's a very difficult idea
we should talk about.
The question is, after we die
and come into this world, why can't
we
remember
where we came from?
That's a really big question.
And if we could remember
where we were before,
if we could simply remember
our previous lives,
then we would all be very friendly
people. There would be no international
conflicts if we
could change our past lives.
I think when we study Buddhism,
we sometimes ask ourselves,
for example, why we do
n't remember, whether we
have a previous life, and why
we can't remember.
It's completely unknown to me,
and I believe if we are truly honest
with ourselves,
many of us can say...
I have this feeling about what I was in
my last life, but
if you're completely honest,
then we have to say I don't really know.
I don't remember exactly
where I was. Sometimes I have this feeling.
For example, I have the feeling I was
a cook in my last life because
his cooking skills are so bad,
but I don't really remember
my past life.
And why is that? And
this whole poem here, the whole
story—
if you
expect to remember, then
you can't
understand where you come from. If you think
you should remember your last life,
then you don't understand where
you come from.
You still have this feeling
that there's someone there who had
a body in a
past life and the same mind.
And in Middle Bay, at Middle
Way School, they say
they believe that Michael is
my consciousness of my thoughts.
The person whose thoughts are allowed is
Maike, and it feels right. Or,
I
have a body.
Schiller has a finger, and that's why
we call them the enemy's finger. So, is there
an Ingo?  Schiller, and he has
these fingers, but
he isn't his fingers,
and the student must be some kind of spirit of
Gis or something,
and this spirit moves from life
to life, so there's a niche, Maike,
and
he dies in this life and leaves
this body on her. You can see it;
we can see that the body
remains here and is burned, but
the student has left,
and
it feels like there must be some kind of real opponent
who goes on,
and
he leaves this body and goes into
another world.
We don't know what happened to the spirit, the
spirit is invisible,
and
you can see the proof of
another person's spirit in their eyes.
You can see that they have a spirit,
and you can see that in their face
and in what they do and what they
say, but you ca
n't see the other person's spirit.
We believe that when the student
leaves this body behind,
the body is still here, but
maybe the killer is
somehow mixed with the spirit described; he has
gone into another world, into another life, and he has left this body behind,
and then the student
Taking on another body, that's how
we talk about it and that's how we think about it. The
student exists within this
body,
and then the body gets old,
and Kaye Scholer leaves this car
and just gets a new car and
drives on. That's how
we feel about it, and that's
the point the first Panchen
Lama talks about. We
think we're
changing cars in such a way that you get out of one car
and get into a new one and just keep driving.
But what he
said is, there is
no body that leaves the old car,
and there is no body that
gets into the new car. That's
not you.
That's not who you are.
You also leave your spirit behind
when you get out of the old car,
leave the old body behind, and
we can all see that.
But you also leave your spirit. You
leave Michael.
It's not like there is a
Michael.
And I know that sounds too good to be true,
but that's a problem of language. It's
not true that he
gets out of his old body,
then goes into Bardot for seven weeks,
49 days,
and then goes into his new body like that.
Isn't that wrong? It's more like,
wait a minute, I need to get the soup, switch it on,
I'll be right back.
My teacher gave me a good talking-to
30 years ago, he
called me the pot burner because I
burned all the pots in the monastery, and it's still like that for me.
So it's not like the church
leaves its body and goes to another place.
And now listen carefully, this is what it's about:
new seeds sprout
and a new sidewalk emerges. I
'm not the type who
changes cars from life to life, it's
not like that. Right now,
my seeds sprout as a killer,
and as a killer's body, and as a
spirit, and these seeds will end,
and then the
vitreous body and the opponent's spirit will also cease to
exist, and new seeds will
sprout.
Ten minutes after I die,
new seeds will sprout, and then at
that moment there is no opponent anymore, there are
only more seeds, more seeds that
sprout, and that is a completely different
person. Of course, they can't
remember what they were before. Of
course, we can't.  No,
it's completely different seeds that sprout.
Of course, he can't remember; there's
no one who could remember. There's
a new body and
a new mind. It's not as if
Nicolas stepped out of his body, like an
old
car, and then got into a new
body, a new car.
Nicolas' old seeds
will simply be
used up, and new seeds will
sprout,
and he will be a completely different person.
And of course, he certainly won't
remember anything because he is a completely different
person or a different mind. And that's
not how we usually talk.
But the point of this section in the
poem is that it's
very interesting,
and I would like to tell my students
how long it takes,
or took, to
become a dog. How long does it take? Is it true
that Nicolas goes into this state for
seven weeks,
and if he's lucky, then chooses a
new car? No, that's not true. The seeds sprout,
65 per second.
So how long does it take to
get into a new car and
get a new mind and
become a new person?
It will  Only 1.65 seconds a second, okay.
I don't know why we feel safe.
If
I die, it's
okay. I have seven weeks to
figure it out, and people will pray for
me, and David will pray for me. It's not that
urgent. I have
seven weeks
to choose my seeds for my
future. And that's not how it is. The seeds
open in 1.65 seconds a second. It's
not even an hour, and
to become my dog, it doesn't even take
a second to become a dog.
You don't have to wait until the
dog's body has grown. That's
not how it is.
Its entire mind, its entire body
can
pass into another body in one second. Just don't think
you have seven weeks to
prepare. The
faster I have, the better. I have seven weeks to
find a good next body. That's
not how it is.
Which seeds you have when you die will
determine what you become, and it's
not your choice. It's not even
your choice to be there.
You have no choice. Which seeds you have
when you die
is what decides what you become.  You
will and you have no right to
talk about it, that if you are good together,
but they will be good and
nice to you, but if you have
done anything wrong then
it will probably go wrong.
So if a part of you
came to you, then one could say, okay,
China is going to Bardot, let's pray for him,
he will hear us, maybe
he can remember his good seeds.
And unfortunately, that's not how it is. You are gone, you
leave your bodies, you leave
your old car, and you also leave
the old driver,
and you become a new car and
a new driver.
And this
[music], let's
go with the lyrics briefly,
even if that means that they
probably won't be finished in 100 years.
He says, look at
these,
these wonder beings, they are so
powerful, you have to
imagine it.
This is a possibility for a
future life. There is
this children's game with the
moment, a
marble game, a
children's game,
that's how it works for them. They play
with planets and can
stroll around with them. It doesn't just do Ironman, okay,
if they have fun,
then you can have a whole  Carving planets,
for example Mars, over the sun,
they are very powerful,
but they also have the problem that
they think the pen
was made in Japan and that they bought the pen.
They still think that way.
They have wonderful seeds that are just
sprouting.
They have the power to play with entire planets
like baseball,
and yet they don't understand why. They don't
understand that everyone saw it.
Everything depends on seeds that sprout. Okay,
and how can they, how can anything
begin?
How do things begin?
And we can talk for a long time about
how something good started in your life
or why something bad
starts in your life, but to put it briefly,
you can't point to the moment
when this pen became a pen.
You can say the students, this pen was
made in Japan.
Then on November 3,
2020,
it came out of the factory. But what
was the
exact time when it became a pen?
You can't find that moment. You won't
find that moment when
this pen became a pen. Then
they finished it. It was at 9:39:10.
At that moment, it was already coming out of the factory,
but was that the point at which
the front part or the back part was
taken out of the factory? It doesn't really
matter by what time, maybe ten
minutes. That's why new ones came out of the factory.
But actually,
and it's a very difficult idea,
part of the pen must have come out of the factory first,
and this part of the pen came out,
and then the end came out. There's
a time difference between
the time when the front part of the
pen came out of the factory—that's
not ten minutes and 14 milliseconds—
and the back part of the pen came
out of the factory ten minutes later, at 9 and 15 milliseconds. But then the
middle part came out of the factory. Does that even matter? There must have been
14 and a half million customers.
Yes, but when did half of the pen come out, the
front part, and when did
the back part of the pen come out? I'm
interested because listen, you ca
n't tell me when the pen
came out of the factory because there are
parts of the time that are too short.  than that
he could observe them, only a
second. Every second has a beginning
and an end, and every second in
time has a
beginning of time and an end of
that time as well, and it lasts for a certain amount of time. Part-time
begins and
time ends, okay, but
these should
be smaller periods of time, a sub-section. Okay, but you ca
n't see these shorter periods of time. Listen,
I'm planning to
bake a cake for my wife today. They say
that's not healthy, but I don't care.
It doesn't make you healthy, but it makes
you happy when you're sick. True,
and this cake will have many parts.
True, there will be a top part
and a middle part, and there
will be a bottom part of the cake.
And if the parts are too small for
you to see, if
you can't see the atoms of the cake,
then you can't
see any part of the cake at all. If you can't see the
parts of a cake, then you ca
n't see the cake.
I know that I can't see the atoms of the cake,
that's 20, but if you
fit many atoms of a cake together, then you can see it.
Hill, do you understand that?  Not if you fit many
cake atoms together and
say, "Now I can see, now
it's not so small anymore," but even
then there must still be an atom here
and another atom here, and you
think that the corner of the atoms... If you ca
n't see the corners of the atoms,
then you can't see the cake.
The point is, the cake isn't made
of atoms, but the cake comes from
you. Okay, time doesn't come towards you,
but it comes from
rebirth in another body, to
another mind. It doesn't come to you;
it comes from you. It can't come to you.
The atoms in this
pen can't come to you; you ca
n't see them. It's too
small; you can't see them at all. And
if something is too small for you to
see, and you put many of them together,
then you still would
n't be able to see the corner. That would be
the corner of an atom. And if
you can't see the end of the pen,
then it means the pen comes from
you and not from its side.
And if you hope
that you have a pretty good life...  If you had
and
did some pretty good things,
then after you die you'll get
a
pretty cool car, that's
a false idea. There are
no new cars and no
new drivers.
They're simply
more things that come from the seeds.
Nobody watches what comes from the seeds.
You are what comes from the seeds.
You don't watch what comes from
your seeds. You are what comes from their seeds.
The
viewer comes from seeds. Don't think
your body belongs to you, your house belongs to you,
your job—all of that
comes from seeds. Nobody owns
your job,
nobody owned your house, and
nobody gets a new car.
It's really very interesting, and all
these things in your life, all the
colors, all the shades, the
shapes, they come from the seeds, and
the person who sows them also comes from them.
And there's nobody else. There's
nobody who had the seeds. There's no such
thing. Okay, let's
move on to the next verse.
And there's a story
that these people
have beautiful children, and
they're called Heike, daughters, and
Sons of the Qatar,
and when the
Daevas
look at children,
they feel a strong
connection to them,
and they don't understand that
these come from their being.
Someone had a baby,
Veronica, and my friend had
twins last week.
Also,
Veronica's son had twins,
and we had two
human births last week,
and the woman was so happy, and she
sent us a picture of two
boys drinking from her breast. She
has two little boys
drinking from her breast at the same time, and she was
so happy.
And when you have a child,
it feels to me as if
that child has come out of your body,
and you are very proud, and you
are deeply fulfilled. Hyde,
I have given life to another being,
and I am
very strongly drawn to that
being. But here is the first Pantchen
Lama: you don't see your children; you do
n't see in the correct way.
You don't understand where these
children actually come from. They come from
your names.
These children have sprung from the seed,
and you have yourself  You
created them, and you also
created them during pregnancy, and you
also created the children that came from you,
and they are all yours.
And when you understand where your children
truly come from,
and when you see them,
you simply want to be kind to everyone
if you understood who
actually created your children, because they
were your good seeds in your mind.
And sometimes, when we have a family,
I don't know why, but some
people
become more compassionate after having children, and
I've experienced this very often in my life.
People
who were selfish
suddenly become more
compassionate after having children,
and they learn
to sacrifice their own happiness for someone else.
And when I was still in the diamond
business,
I had to hire hundreds of people.
I interviewed them, I had to
find them, I had to
conduct job interviews with them,
I had to train them, and I did this for 19
years, hundreds
and hundreds more people.
And after a few years, I
realized
mothers are great employees.
Mothers are number one.
If you want someone who can
work really well, then look for a mother you
know.  They sacrifice themselves, they
know how to stay up late to finish a
job. The father will
simply lie down when the child
cries, but the mother doesn't go to
bed.
And I've gotten into the habit of looking after them
because they know how to sacrifice something. And sometimes,
if you're someone who has had a child,
you'll see that it makes them feel powerless.
And sometimes—I've never had a child, but
this is my observation—when you
have a child,
your mental poisons become stronger.
You have
more responsibilities, you get
more angry, you become more
selfish in some ways. You'll
take care of your own child, but you don't take care
of other people's children.
You have prejudices and think you
should take care of your own child,
but I don't have to take care of my
neighbor's child, at least not in the
same way.
And what they're talking about here
is the misunderstanding or the misinterpretation of
where your children come from. And
they're using the children of the device here.
You know how we have children?
They
suddenly just appeared in the womb.  Every
day it's simply a child in
your lap that doesn't come from your
body,
it feels kind of sweet, it sounds
so called because it's pretty easy
to have children than yourself, and the idea here
is,
when the children
come out, there are two ways:
number one, you understand that this
wonderful, valuable
knowledge from your name came about
when you shared things with other people,
and when you then have the child,
then you could care even more about the
children of other people, or
if you don't understand where the child
actually comes from,
then that child could become a disaster,
so you protect your own child
and don't care about the children of
other people. It can go both ways,
your child comes, statements,
and if you understand that, then
you also understand
that you should take care of all people's children
equally, in the same way.
Okay, well, there's
an interesting dynamic
here,
your whole life
is
surrounded by
competition, and that's pretty much the same
with rich people, human beings.
Okay,
I was
listening to the radio late one evening when I came home from work, and it
was a nice piece.  Okay, it took me 45
minutes. I
live outside, in the countryside, in
a mountain, and when I
drive home in the evening, it's a dirty
road, but it's a beautiful
drive. Sometimes I hear radio
things from other places, other
states,
really completely different places.
And then I heard these
famous actors, and
yesterday, his interview, which I heard,
and they were talking about the other
actors in the same movie—
these wonderful, beautiful people, very
beautiful-
looking women and men, very
famous.
I don't know why they haven't gotten a bit of a
belly like me.
They still look as beautiful as
before. But the more
physically beautiful a person is,
and the more they are, the more they
get used to
jealousy or competition with other
beautiful people. It's a kind of curse.
It's a really bad problem
for successful, rich,
beautiful people.
They sometimes feel
very competitive with each other,
or even more intensely
jealous of each other online.
And here the Panchen Lama is talking about it.
He says that for these people, they have
a wonderful life.  This
debate,
the one thing that determines their lives, the most
important, the most important part of their
lives, is trying.
It's simply not enough to be the best
actor. It's not enough
to win the acting award. They
look at each other all the time. She
's prettier than me, younger.
He's stronger,
or
he has more fans. There are more people
who follow him than me.
[Music]
And that's what's being talked about here.
These feelings, these feelings, this what,
and they have two of them, two big
feelings. The first, when they have a child,
then they feel this intense love
for their children.
And when they
see a weaver, then they get this
strong jealousy and this
incredible sense of competition
and the squabbling. Lama says deer,
let's think about this device.
Let's think about these beautiful, rich,
and beautiful people.
Two things determine their lives. Number
one,
they have their own children and an
incredible attachment, a bond to
them, an incredible love
for their children. And at the same time,
they carry a strong jealousy of
the other
famous people, the other beautiful
people, these successful beings.
It's really strange that they have such a
strong bond with their  Having children
and at the same time this intense
jealousy of other successful
people, and the Panchen Lama doesn't say here, "
You should be a good person, you
should love other people just as
you love your children." He doesn't say that.
It's really interesting what he says. Do
n't forget
that this is a battle between the
devil and the angel. It's a battle
between the
devil and the angel, and the devil says, "
Look, there are also tastes
in your mind. Are there
thoughts of doubt?" First,
oh,
the compassion and love for your
students is so beautiful. And
second,
great jealousy of others, the teacher,
for example. Okay,
he doesn't say that. He doesn't say the
first band name. He doesn't
say, "
You have good thoughts and you have
bad thoughts,
and please try to have more good
thoughts and try not to have
bad thoughts." He does
n't say that. He says nobody has these thoughts.
He says nobody has these thoughts.
Nobody has this love for their children,
and nobody feels for their
competitors. There's nobody there who has
feelings.  That's the devil
speaking when your [partner] once told you,
please try to have
more loving thoughts
and fewer
thoughts of competition. If
your [partner] studied back then, it's like when
I tell it like this, then they do
n't know what they're talking about.
Because
if I tell them, you should have more good
thoughts, like the ones you have for your
children, witch, or
you shouldn't feel any competition
like you feel for other people
when processing [something]. If I
tell you this, then I'm talking about you,
but you don't even exist. There is
no "you." And as long as we think there's
a duo
that harbors these loving feelings
towards the children, or if we
think there's a "you" who harbors
competitive thoughts, then you've already
lost the war. Then you've already
lost the war. I'll say it again:
if you think there's a "you" who harbors
loving thoughts, and if you
think there's a "you" who harbors
competitive thoughts, and if
you think you should have loving
thoughts and that the duo
should feel less jealousy, then you've
already lost the battle.  Then you're listening to the devil
because there is no you,
nobody has these thoughts, the signs. Why are
you leaving us in this class? At
least one thing is certain that I
could improve,
and if there isn't anything
that could get worse if I did
n't study, then
why do we even have this lesson? There is no
you, there are only seeds, okay? There is
no you,
nobody got out of the old car
and got into the new one. A
man lives his own life, has his own children,
and has the success of other people. There is
no you, there are only seeds that
open up. There are only seeds that
sprout.
Gisela Winter, no "I give you, can I
then be happy?" Who then becomes
a Buddha?
Nobody becomes a brother
type, or seeds sprout.
Then you are a Buddha,
understood? So don't worry
about anything.
By the way, I hear someone. The
Turner's microphone, please. There is
no "I" that has
happy thoughts. There is no "
I" that has the unhappiest thoughts.
You are the seeds, you are your seeds that sprout.
So don't worry
about anything. I'd rather worry
about the...  Seeds, when you
experience yourself as loving with your
children, then you see your
own loving, because your seed of
love grows as they emerge.
[Music]
If you
feel competition, then it's just
collecting for a competition.
Okay, what am I supposed to do there? I understand,
try to
understand.
You watch as seeds open, and
you have to
focus on them, not on that.
I
focus exclusively on the seeds.
Okay,
I have problems with meditating. I
know that the seeds that open... You
watch as they open together.
Okay, that's the last one for today, and then
we'll do a Q&A.
Okay,
I've told this story a few
times already,
and I tell so many stories throughout
the year. I don't know, I can't
remember
everything I've already told. Let me show you my
kitchen,
and when I wake up at night,
I go into the kitchen to get
something to snack on so
my wife doesn't hear. And there's
always water on the
floor here, and I always put it in there,
and every  At night, very, very quietly,
I accidentally kicked out the water. It was
really cold, even in winter it's cold
here, and the water was really cold.
And then I felt responsible for it.
I thought it should
be someone else, I should clean up the water. So
I got on my knees and cleaned
it up. And I thought to myself,
maybe my...
maybe we somehow...
or the dishwasher is broken.
And
I dried the floor for five or six
nights. Every night
I got on my knees and cleaned up
the water. And all of a sudden,
I don't even know what happened,
I thought I was fed up with drying up the water, cleaning up the water.
Maybe there's a leaking pipe somewhere,
and I should fix it.
It's so much work, cleaning up the water every
night. Maybe
I should find out where the
water came from. And that's what we learn here: do
n't focus on the result,
focus on the...
And I called my friend Daniel
Garcia, and he came,
and he looked under the...
and he took care of the pipe.  took care of it
and fixed it, okay, and what the SC
Panchen Lama is saying here is that you should
only think about
your seeds, don't focus on
the result,
just take care of your statements,
and if you feel very strong love for your
children
and strong jealousy at work,
then that also comes from the seeds, and take care of
that, don't take care of
that. I'm
not thinking about the magical Meike
Böschemeyer,
think about the love, and under her, from the
seeds comes, and the jealousy
also comes from statements,
and Gesche Michael's
jealousy also comes from seeds, and
Gesche Michael's love comes from
st,
so work on your seeds, work
under the sink, find the pipe
and fix it, that's okay, the pipe is yours,
the problem is that the person who
fixes the pipe also comes from seeds, the
person who works on the seeds is
also a result of seeds, therefore, no matter
what statements you have, they will make
you a better
worker or a worse
worker, and nobody escapes,
nobody has control over
what witnesses say or create.
People who work with seeds,
if there's a problem with the seeds,
then there's also a problem with
the one who planted the seeds.
Okay,
that sounds kind of like his things, like
a vicious cycle.
It sounds like we ca
n't improve.
It's difficult, but
it's not impossible. As long as you
understand
that things come from seeds, there is
hope,
and if you forget that, then there is
no hope. So focus on
this, focus on this.
If you have bad seeds,
then it's because you yourself came from bad
seeds. How can I
fix that then? How can I fix my
bad seeds
if I myself
come from bad seeds? That seems
impossible. You can do small things,
okay? And we are very lucky that the
seeds grow. That is our luck
that the seeds double, double, double,
double. You
can do something small and nice today,
any small, kind gesture. Then there is
hope
because these seeds will become more, more, more, and more, and bigger, bigger, bigger.
And
today,
a very practical step: if you
want to have a good rebirth,
then just do something.
Okay, a little something good, that's a reason, something small and good.
I'm making a
super thing, it's not particularly
tasty.
I'm not a very good cook,
my Tibetan is better than my
cooking skills,
but I make small, nice things for other
people and
dedicate these new seeds. Okay, and let's all dedicate
the good things
so that there will be an international
solution for the conflicts, for
the tensions. Let
's do something small, like a
soup. We don't know how our
mornings will turn out, whether I
'll burn them or not. The soup
makes something small and good
and dedicates it to this, and then the seed will
grow exponentially, will explode,
the little seed, and let it grow.
That's our only hope.
Okay, team,
you have questions for me.
We have something after 20 minutes or so.
Okay, the many that you taught us,
my honor, thank you that every franc,
it is these friends, continues with what
you said about not being on
this night, also that I have some
questions that can be answered when we
talk about the matter from the
different schools, for example.  Even just an
hour, the seeds of
art are gathered near the heart,
and in the
upper part of the middle path, it is
said that the seeds are gathered within me,
or where the things come from.
The questions and questions arose, so can
you talk more about why we are
told we are gathered within us?
And now you say one should
n't focus on oneself but
also focus on the seeds. That sounds
like the seeds are outside of me,
not inside me. That's a good question. Do
you see the lower schools
saying "good" means a
nice person,
so good to plant? And when you die,
you want to get a new body, a
good body, and you will be in
a beautiful place.
That is
the first movement of the wheel. That is
how I taught the beginners:
please do good things,
and they will die.
You want to have a good rebirth, so
please do good things. Say "planting
material" is to have it. Then you can see
how a backpack in the next life,
and you can do it there too,
namely
what the first bachelor said. Do
n't forget
that the
middle, the one with the seeds...  Working on a
statement comes from the bed at the same
moment,
so at the
same moment when the person tries to
improve their seeds,
the person who is slim with the new good seeds, at
that moment they
also make statements, do you understand, the seed
skitter
also comes, exceptions,
so if you understand that then you have
a chance, but if you
believe that it is a gentle one,
honestly, expenses come at the same
moment,
then you have problems,
you have problems,
so try to understand
that the seed plants
also make statements, for example,
if the seed plants
are in a good mood today,
then the seed and plant area is
good to plant together, and if the
plant is in a bad mood,
he cannot put them together,
so you have to understand that
statements also come,
and we have to
make space for these plants that are so good for us,
the seed plants, the one who
sees the land coming together, also comes, so what then, so
we have to be attentive
and the right seed plants
so that there is a good plate,
so we have to take time to
think about
why
I am happy to
plant together, why I understand, why
I believe in it  It's something
special
that you believe in yourself, and
that's the root of everything.
What the first one says has been here for a long time:
take care of the seeds, think about it, why do
you
even want to come to this class?
You've said it before, but
then I looked carefully at these things, taking care of these things,
losing this year, which
always means when other people do something good,
that's when I saw it, saw it, and wanted to pretend that what
you do,
this whole thing with the returns
café meditation, he reports that on
others,
that's the true seed to
make yourself 2 against his plants, so we'll go for your
velvet land together, what's the best way
for that,
also tells other people how cool they are
and says do it all the time and do
n't lie about it, and
he finds nothing, you will be great
if that, if the person is a so
then I don't say that they are a good
person, that the tea doesn't let go, I don't
say that,
I say if you see someone doing something
really beautiful,
then go and say how cool, that's kind of it, even
if it does
n't tell other people how cool they are  Are
pensions, which is great, and where I
saw how you spoke to that difficult
person today, that's so
cool.
I saw how patient you were.
I just want to
compliment you on that. I wish I could have as
much patience as you.
Building up other people who make
promises makes
you two Westminsters yourself. That
's really great,
ball in it,
and don't tell them cool like
seed plants, honestly, if they
are really cool,
and that makes us the best
plants. That's all that the only one
can do, even back then, to show
where we are limited. I believe that only the
whole school is very helpful. Word
just finished his first book. Woods finished his
first book.
Yes, it's about them, just examples. I
think it's the best book about the
UN, but no school ever
translated it.
I believe it's the very best book
I've ever seen about the school,
and
it's already published. The one with
Kathpress
Online
Enterprise called the book "The Golden
Key."
And if you really want to understand the local,
then give her the book and chew on it
and ask, "Was Dr.
Ask that?"  It will be with him
teaching the classes about it, that's why
I read something from it and it
really blew me away. He's from
Georgia to the Cape, who is always right, and
he said
if you really
understand the spirit school
and its ideas about the refrigerator
where you watch the collectors,
if you understand that, then you
can practice tantra so that the
diamond weighs most successfully, then
you will learn secret teachings, then you can
experience them if you really understand. That's why
I was like, wow, that's really cool.
I want to
encourage you to study this book. Many
people have told me. I
bought the ebook.
It's an instant, immediate
success experience. You order,
so there's no opting out. That's not
what you need. Not on the postal
routes
in America, for example, like when you
order something, but sometimes it takes two
years until it arrives, not what the
customer
receives in less than a minute.
I'm told
that they're just the same. I don't want to make it so
complicated. There are
two things you should know, and
eat goose
if a book is very heavy.  If
you don't understand it,
then in my
opinion you don't need to
buy it anymore because you already
understand it. If you simply don't understand the world, just
because you don't understand it,
I mean you don't need to
buy it anymore because there's no
reason to buy it. If you
understand the topic anyway, why should
you buy it? In
my opinion, it's almost a
tradition that we should
buy the books we don't understand.
Why
[Music]
should we buy the books we don't understand at all?
Because only through this do things go well.
And these mixed NATO mines have been working for
five or six years,
and each of them has
their own book. Very good. I would like to show
you almost every team. Can I do that?
[Music]
Let me see if I can find it. Sure, sure.
You can
still share the screen. Okay, here we go.
We'll show you that this
week in the mixed class,
can you see that?
[Music]
That's in the next one.
These are the topics. There's space.
A
secret preview will be told. No
more
preview.  Secretly
prescribed,
these are the original ones to wear. Where is
everything? He came 2005 years earlier,
translate 6 successes.
Here is
[music].
It is his. Then
comes, then come Adam's books from
the 18th century,
1800 years earlier. There comes the only
school as
1700 years earlier,
masters there marked and all the
logical logic schools, how one should think.
That is 1500 years earlier,
and then the great moral schools,
like, well, that is 1300 years to follow.
Then comes
the great translators in China, who
translated from China, like Master Jan See, and
then comes the lower part of the middle.
You can see the
great writers,
and they still have the meditation,
and they wrote the great books
about the girls. That was
1300 years ago. They wrote the great
guide to meditation, and
then we came to the higher middle way. That
is mostly derstandard.at.
They really understood the majority very well,
truly extraordinary
people, that this was about 1300 years
earlier.
[music]
Then came loud, already like  One develops a good
heart,
that can happen 1000 years ago,
then came the first
[music],
the global years about 600 million years ago,
then came the fact that students of different
schools proved themselves in two different ways
because all the great schools to study,
these are the great ideas of the last
2500 years. Now I want to show you
what's coming, now you are ready for it,
I see you are very interested. Here I
am, I'll make it all a
little smaller,
and here
we translate from it, on the sides
here we translate six in there
and 33
are already finished, and the whole thing buys
the super of the heritage, only rapid medicine
or
commentary on the diamond cutter Sutter,
commentary on
heart death,
every big theme here from
ancient times is commemorated by the next
victim. On the
left and right you see the books,
love to translate text and they cover
the big theme, every big theme
from the last 2000 becomes today a value
from the mix, during the day self-mixed
books are here on the side
and there are 27 translations, and if
you don't  If you're worried, then you must be crazy, just crazy. Anyway,
if I have it now, then
this week we'll have 60
classes
about this idea. I saved it.
You asked me,
you always asked me about the spirit school.
If you really wanted to understand it,
and where they tell you they're laid out,
then come and read. Mixa has classes. There are
27 different books that we're
currently translating that cover all of this.
Thinking that we have one last
question,
this is a
trained question from several.
They asked a person, for
example, that their partner
no longer loves them and the family
no longer gives and
wants to leave the family, and asked someone else.
They themselves no longer have any means
for other people and are no
longer able to really listen
or add effectively. What are the advice you can
give in two
different situations, but it's
somehow the same if someone doesn't want
compassion and love? I like
this question. Who is one of the
saddest things in the world? On the
one hand,
is in a relationship and
it looks like the other
person is losing interest.
They don't live as much as
they did at the beginning, and
it  It's
devastating, it feels like
water is seeping through your fingers,
and it can be seen while you're doing it. We're seeing what's happening,
and it's very, very
sad.
You have a student,
this person also had feelings, but
now it looks like the
feelings are there. On the other side,
you're the person who's losing their feelings,
and you used to care a lot about these
people and they were very important to you, for
example, a family, your job, or your
partner, and now I don't want that
passion anymore. Now I don't feel
love anymore.
Instead, I feel
[Music].
Now I only feel
responsible. I had to be because of this.
This is my family, this
is my partner,
this is the company that has given me
work for many years. I have no passion. I don't give any
passion
anymore, but I still feel
I owe them something,
and both are feelings.
I owe them love because it's my
family. I don't have that anymore,
and that's very unpleasant. Or
my family, or in my
company, they don't seem to
have that passion anymore. About myself,
how does it look, and these two...  Feelings
are actually the same, thirst he says,
it feels the same. Love is
lost, dear guests of
camps, what can we do then?
Happiness
is
the law of karma, that small little
seeds can grow very quickly.
The first law of karma states
that they double every 24
hours. If you understand them well,
that's very cool,
it's a super fertilizer.
If you then understand,
then the customers will say that the
plants grew
gigantic,
let this one grow bigger.
If you see that love goes from it, there's
never anything going on, just trying.
I try to get the water to the hallway.
Someday lose it, rather repair
that leak where the water comes from.
I am
[Music] I would have a
long life, I've seen a
lot, I have love, I've seen it often.
I don't think it
works that way, that you go there to
the person and talk to them and
say, "Hey, it looks like you don't
live with me as much anymore. Can you
please try harder? You have a
family, you have a few,
you are important to us. Please have more love
for us, even if I can't, I  Showing that this
definitely doesn't work
because it comes from lonely people. How much
love they have for you comes from
loneliness,
so you just have to plant the right things
by giving me love,
and you can do that by forgetting the net.
Because then the people who help you, someone, someone
works on the ears,
orange plantations, in my
team,
someone has the coffee and planted around
a café.
When I, when he
drinks, someone planted the watermelons,
so many people care
about me,
I should give him some love. Even then,
I live.
[Music]
outside, I know the mountains, but
someone
sends me electricity. Thank you.
I don't know where you will be, but I mean,
bills are paid, there
is more electricity
around me. It's fine even though it
's cold outside, and just try to
be grateful for
all the beautiful things you have in your
life. These
are this
[Music]
life. This love will go back.
Rather, set a big thing. The love
of a godparent, hear the love of family
at home, love your family towards
other people, love towards yourself.
You can do the new  Plant, you can
rekindle this fire by
finding other people now,
that you keep my house warm, then missing
for the coffee beans,
thank you so much for the internet, thank you so much for
mobilizing these classes
and that little crazy one works day
and night so that
we get these opportunities,
show other people your gratitude
and
the love worth returning, and it's so
exciting when it comes back,
works because it comes through seeds,
it's very, very
when you, how you bring the love
back to your actual last
or also from other people from
a family, it's to stand
that you have orders
from
further away, it's
like fixing the pipes, much
more gratitude, saw then specifically
say then be ready,
okay,
see you tomorrow, yes,
and thank you so much, I mean it seriously,
fighting,
I know, once a big, big team, the
internet, stand and play, then
I know that his huge group
of volunteers went, then translate,
I know whose head, it's really
beautiful, I today that I don't know how
he does it